{
    "data": [
        {
            "id": "c04d5b5ba5805a22402b8893d1f64cd7",
            "title": "A U.S.-China Trade War With Students and Tourists as Potential Pawns",
            "description": "With travel warnings and revoked visas, the two superpowers locked in a bruising trade war may make students and tourists their bargaining chips.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "U.S.",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "China",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "students",
                    "label": "NORP"
                },
                {
                    "text": "tourists",
                    "label": "NORP"
                },
                {
                    "text": "trade war",
                    "label": "EVENT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "9af329f383ab03be6a888545389c21d1",
            "title": "Keith Siegel, a Former Hostage, Recounts Captivity in Gaza",
            "description": "Keith Siegel, who spent 484 days as a hostage, described the physical and psychological distress he endured, in an interview with The New York Times.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Keith Siegel",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Gaza",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "The New York Times",
                    "label": "ORG"
                },
                {
                    "text": "484 days",
                    "label": "DATE"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "84a39c4339fa1d1713e0f5e77f6ee3c8",
            "title": "UK Supreme Court Says Trans Women Are Not Legally Women Under Equality Act",
            "description": "Britain’s Supreme Court ruled that the word “woman” refers to biological sex under the country’s anti-discrimination law, in a blow to trans rights activists.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "UK",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Supreme Court",
                    "label": "ORG"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Britain",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Equality Act",
                    "label": "LAW"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "c302d2ffa80839e92af942dc8d107e60",
            "title": "Its Journalism Challenged Autocrats. Trump Wants to Silence It.",
            "description": "Journalists at Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty who have been imprisoned for their work are dismayed by the effort to close the outlet.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Trump",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Radio Free Europe/Radio Liberty",
                    "label": "ORG"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "23690457ab59d9fcdb840ccbb181fd90",
            "title": "Italy’s Meloni Heads to Washington to Meet Trump. Will It Pay Off for Europe?",
            "description": "The stakes are high as Giorgia Meloni, a conservative who shares some of Mr. Trump’s nationalist ideology, meets with him on Thursday as his trade war has frayed nerves worldwide.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Italy",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Meloni",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Washington",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Trump",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Europe",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Giorgia Meloni",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Thursday",
                    "label": "DATE"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "1b06c9bc94a5936c6b7449b17a4c32a3",
            "title": "Israel Threatens Further Escalation in Gaza War",
            "description": "The United Nations warned that the humanitarian situation in Gaza was likely at its worst since the conflict began and that the population was again on the brink of famine.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Israel",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Gaza",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "The United Nations",
                    "label": "ORG"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "738079c73b83e64f2a3f62e2c155569b",
            "title": "R.S.F. in Sudan Declare Parallel Government Amid Assault on Zamzam Camp",
            "description": "The United Nations said that at least 300 people were killed when the armed group, the Rapid Support Forces, stormed a camp in Darfur.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "R.S.F.",
                    "label": "ORG"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Sudan",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "The United Nations",
                    "label": "ORG"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Rapid Support Forces",
                    "label": "ORG"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Darfur",
                    "label": "GPE"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "cb73588d16de57598874bbadf4d8c434",
            "title": "Bukele Has Power to Return Deportee in El Salvador to U.S., Experts Say",
            "description": "Experts say President Nayib Bukele has the power but not the interest to return a man deported from Maryland to El Salvador in error.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Bukele",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "El Salvador",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "U.S.",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Nayib Bukele",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Maryland",
                    "label": "GPE"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "dc2e68a0357ec65d5974b8e5e96ff9cc",
            "title": "Latvia Exits Land Mine Convention Amid Fears of Russian Aggression",
            "description": "The government, along with two other Baltic nations and Poland, agreed last month to quit the 1997 accord that prohibits from using anti-personnel mines. Russia’s invasion of Ukraine was cited as a key reason.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Latvia",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Baltic",
                    "label": "LOC"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Poland",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Russia",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Ukraine",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "1997",
                    "label": "DATE"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "e39ddfa02816a33ab0b9c2a983ea3df3",
            "title": "Peru’s Former First Lady Flees as She and Ex-President Are Sentenced to Prison",
            "description": "Former President Ollanta Humala and his wife, Nadine Heredia, were sentenced on Tuesday to 15 years in prison for money laundering. Brazil granted her diplomatic asylum, officials said.",
            "ner": [
                {
                    "text": "Peru",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "First Lady",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Ollanta Humala",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Nadine Heredia",
                    "label": "PERSON"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Brazil",
                    "label": "GPE"
                },
                {
                    "text": "Tuesday",
                    "label": "DATE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}